export const QuizDataReact = [
    {
        question: "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        options:[ "Original DOM","Virtual DOM","Both A and B","None of the above."],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port where webpack-server runs?",
        options:[ "8080","3000", "3030", "6060"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many numbers of elements a valid react component can return?",
        options: ["2", "5", "1", "3"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What does ES6 stand for?",
        options: ["ECMAJavaScript 6", "ECMAScript 6", "EJavaScript 6", "ECMA 6"],
        answer:2
    },

    {
        question: "What does props stand for?",
        options: ["Proper Arguments", "Properties", "Proper Return Values", "All the above"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which keyword is used for class inheritance?",
        options: ["Extends", "Child", "extend", "inherit"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which method refers to the parent class?",
        options: ["parent()", "top()", "main()", "super()"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question: "Which method is used to generate lists?",
        options: ["map()", "generate()", "new()", "maps()"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which are the keywords to define variables?",
        options: ["var", "let", "Const", "All the above"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question: "JSX allows us to write? ",
        options: ["jQuery in React", "Angular Code in React", "MySQL in React", "HTML in React"],
        answer:4
    },
];